Hello everyone, this video is only for knowledge
purpose if you want to take other financial
decisions,
then we are in the chart of ICC Lombard General Insurance,
so see, right now a
round dish pattern was forming in it,
I had told in the analysis on TV, but
I did not know that it would breakout because
today only your news came that ICC
Bank has confirmed its increase in stock price, so
due to that news
such a good move has come, so now see,
if we take its target
till your breakout point and if we drag it and
place it around the breakout point, the
target has also been achieved, it could
not be sustained after achieving the target, before that it has
resisted and come down, so see, there is
another reason for it resisting, this is
our zone, we should look at it like this, supply
pressure and the whole candle, there is
no hui, it means it was
full selling pressure,
you can also see the volume, so after registering the same zone,
our downward movement was
given in it, so the price tries to break the supply zone.
So only after that it
gives a break out,
if we see that
today our price has
registered around 0.618 and 0.78
and from below if we see in the request
how far it can go to take support, then
our nearest support will be
of 0.5 and below that
our level will be of 0.61, then we
will delete the next one, so see, right now
our zone
from 1144 to your
1071 will reduce the strong support and
if we see the resistance on the upper side,
our nearest resistance will be four, this zone
which is
from 1254 to yours, we have to go
to the setting around 1269, we have to band it from your minute, so
now if we go
according to Delhi temperature, if we draw, the
support will be from
1172 to yours,
right now our resistance will be, the zone which was
resisted was from 128 to
yours,
around 1221, so right now we
cannot draw any pattern because today  On this
day, our move of 8.27% is given in it,
we will see that it can be
made from the nearby area
which is from our 114 to your
1171, we will
try
once the nearest
consolidated zone is
from 1178 to your
1091, both of these are important zones and the
resistance that we are going to face above this is from
1280 to your
1221, we also have to go to the settings for this, it should be
shown in minutes and
if we drop our support which is below that, we will
see from 1144 to your 1057,
then this will also be a strong support, we will
move from 1163 to your 1174, we will zoom a little in the 15 minute time frame, if
you liked the video then please like and
subscribe.